<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>dragonplayer.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Dragon Player</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Dragon Player</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Přehrávač Dragon</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Dragon Player</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Dragon Player</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">Dragon Player (Reproductor Dragon)</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">Dragon 플레이어</name>
  <name xml:lang="nds">Drakenspeler</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Dragon Player</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Odtwarzacz Dragon</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Dragon Player</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Dragon Player</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Prehrávač Dragon</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr">Змајев плејер</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-Latn">Zmajev plejer</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Змајев плејер</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Zmajev plejer</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Dragon videospelare</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Програвач Dragon</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxDragon Playerxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">影音播放_DragonPlayer</name>
  <description>
    <p>
      Dragon Player is a multimedia player where the focus is on simplicity, instead of features. Dragon Player does one thing,
      and only one thing, which is playing multimedia files. It's simple interface is designed not to get in your way and instead
      empower you to simply play multimedia files.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El Dragon Player és un reproductor multimèdia que se centra en la simplicitat, en lloc de les característiques. El Dragon Player fa una cosa, i només una cosa, la qual és reproduir fitxers multimèdia. Té un interfície senzilla, la qual està dissenyada per a que no s'interposi en el vostre camí i que simplement pugueu reproduir els fitxers multimèdia.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Dragon Player is a multimedia player where the focus is on simplicity, instead of features. Dragon Player does one thing, and only one thing, which is playing multimedia files. It's simple interface is designed not to get in your way and instead empower you to simply play multimedia files.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Dragon Player es un reproductor multimedia centrado en la simplicidad en lugar de las características. Hace una cosa, y solo una cosa: reproducir archivos multimedia. Su sencilla interfaz no está diseñada para ponerse en tu camino, sino para ayudarte a reproducir archivos multimedia fácilmente.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">Dragon 플레이어는 기능보다 간단함에 초점을 맞춘 멀티미디어 재생기입니다. Dragon 플레이어는 오직 멀티미디어 파일만을 재생합니다. 동영상 감상을 방해하지 않도록 인터페이스는 간결하게 설계되었습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nds">Drakenspeler is en Multimedia-Afspeler, bi den de Eenfachheit in'n Vörgrund steiht un nich de velen Funkschonen bito. Drakenspeler deit nau een Saak, un dat is dat Afspelen vun Multimedia-Dateien. De Brukerböversiet schall Di nich in de Mööt kamen, man Di bi't Bruken vun Multimedia-Inholden ünnerstütten.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Dragon Player is een multimediaspeler waar de focus ligt op eenvoud, in plaats van functies. Dragon Player doet een ding en alleen een ding, en dat is afspelen van multimediabestanden. Zijn eenvoudige interface is niet ontworpen om in de weg te zitten en in plaats u de mogelijkheid te geven om gewoon multimediabestanden af te spelen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Odtwarzacz Dragon jest odtwarzaczem multimedialnym, gdzie położono nacisk na prostotę, a nie na możliwości. Odtwarzacz Dragon robi jedną rzecz i tylko jedną tj. odtwarzanie plików multimedialnych. Jego prosty układ sterowania został zaprojektowany tak, aby nie wchodził w drogę, ale aby pomagał przy odtwarzaniu plików multimedialnych.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Dragon Player é um leitor multimédia em que o foco é a simplicidade em vez das funcionalidades. O Dragon Player faz uma coisa e apenas uma, que é reproduzir ficheiros multimédia. A sua interface simples é desenhada para não se intrometer e sim ajudá-lo a reproduzir ficheiros multimédia de forma simples.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Dragon Player é um reprodutor multimídia com foco na simplicidade e não em funcionalidades. Ele faz uma coisa e apenas isso, que é a reprodução de arquivos multimídia. Sua interface simples é projetada para não atrapalhá-lo e simplesmente reproduzir arquivos multimídia.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Dragon Player je multimediálny prehrávač, ktorý sa zameriava na jednoduchosť namiesto funkcií. Dragon Player robí jednu vec, a nič iné, ktorou je prehrávania multimediálnych súborov. Jeho jednoduché rozhranie je zavrhnuté, aby nebolo rušivé a aby s ním bolo jednoducho možné prehrávať multimediálne súbory.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Змајев плејер је мултимедијални плејер са тежиштем на једноставности уместо на могућностима. Има једну и само једну намену: пуштање мултимедијалних фајлова. Пружа једноставно сучеље које вас не замара детаљима, већ омогућава да једноставно пуштате мултимедијалне фајлове.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-Latn">Zmajev plejer je multimedijalni plejer sa težištem na jednostavnosti umesto na mogućnostima. Ima jednu i samo jednu namenu: puštanje multimedijalnih fajlova. Pruža jednostavno sučelje koje vas ne zamara detaljima, već omogućava da jednostavno puštate multimedijalne fajlove.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Змајев плејер је мултимедијални плејер са тежиштем на једноставности уместо на могућностима. Има једну и само једну намену: пуштање мултимедијалних фајлова. Пружа једноставно сучеље које вас не замара детаљима, већ омогућава да једноставно пуштате мултимедијалне фајлове.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Zmajev plejer je multimedijalni plejer sa težištem na jednostavnosti umesto na mogućnostima. Ima jednu i samo jednu namenu: puštanje multimedijalnih fajlova. Pruža jednostavno sučelje koje vas ne zamara detaljima, već omogućava da jednostavno puštate multimedijalne fajlove.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Dragon videospelare är en multimediaspelare med fokus på enkelhet istället för funktioner. Dragon videospelare gör endast en sak, nämligen spela multimediafiler. Dess enkla gränssnitt är konstruerat för att inte vara i vägen utan istället ge dig möjlighet att enkelt spela upp multimediafiler.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Програвач Dragon — програма для відтворення мультимедійних даних, основною перевагою якої є простота. Програвач Dragon робить одну річ і лише одну річ, а саме, відтворює файли мультимедійних даних. Простий інтерфейс програми просто не дасть вам зробити щось неправильно, але надасть вам змогу відтворити потрібні вам дані.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxDragon Player is a multimedia player where the focus is on simplicity, instead of features. Dragon Player does one thing, and only one thing, which is playing multimedia files. It's simple interface is designed not to get in your way and instead empower you to simply play multimedia files.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">Dragon Player 是一套多媒體播放器，重點在簡單而非多樣功能。Dragon Player 只做一件事：播放多媒體檔案。</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Característiques:</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Vlastnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Características:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">기능:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nds">Markmalen:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Mogelijkheden:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Możliwości:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Características:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Funkcie:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Могућности:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-Latn">Mogućnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Могућности:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Mogućnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Funktioner:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Можливості:</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxFeatures:xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">功能：</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Simple Interface</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Interfície senzilla</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Simple Interface</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Interfaz sencilla</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">간단한 인터페이스</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Eenfach Böversiet</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Eenvoudig interface</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Prosty układ sterowania</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Interface Simples</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Interface simples</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Jednoduché rozhranie</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Једноставно сучеље.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Jednostavno sučelje.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Једноставно сучеље.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Jednostavno sučelje.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Enkelt gränssnitt</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">простий інтерфейс;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSimple Interfacexx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">簡易介面</li>
      <li>Resuming videos: Starts playing a video where you were watching it last time</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Continua els vídeos: Inicia la reproducció d'un vídeo on l'estàveu veient l'última vegada</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Resuming videos: Starts playing a video where you were watching it last time</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Reanudar vídeos: empieza la reproducción de un vídeo donde lo habías dejado la última vez</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">동영상 위치 기억: 마지막으로 본 지점부터 동영상을 다시 재생합니다</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Videos wiederspelen: En Video dor wieder afspelen, woneem Du vördem ophollen hest</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Video's hervatten: begin met het afspelen van een video waar u de laatste keer deze bekeek</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Wznawianie filmów: Rozpoczyna odtwarzane filmu od chwili jego przerwania przy poprzednim oglądaniu</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Prosseguir os vídeos: Começa a reproduzir um vídeo a partir do local onde o estava a ver da última vez</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Continuação da reprodução de vídeos: Começa a reprodução de um vídeo no ponto em que parou de assistir</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Pokračovanie videa: Spustí prehrávanie videa, kde ste pozerali naposledy</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Настављање видеа: започиње пуштање видеа тамо где сте последње пут стали.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Nastavljanje videa: započinje puštanje videa tamo gde ste poslednje put stali.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Настављање видеа: започиње пуштање видеа тамо где сте последње пут стали.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Nastavljanje videa: započinje puštanje videa tamo gde ste poslednje put stali.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Återuppta videor: Börjar spela en video på stället du senast tittade på den</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">поновлення відтворення відео: відео починає відтворюватися з того моменту, на якому ви зупинили відтворення під час попереднього сеансу роботи з програмою;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxResuming videos: Starts playing a video where you were watching it last timexx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">回復影片：從上次看到的地方開始播放影片</li>
      <li>Support for subtitles: Automatically loads subtitles with the matching name</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Implementació per a subtítols: Càrrega automàticament els subtítols que coincideixen amb el nom</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Support for subtitles: Automatically loads subtitles with the matching name</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Permite subtítulos: carga automáticamente los subtítulos con el mismo nombre</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">자막 지원: 파일 이름이 동일한 자막을 자동으로 불러옵니다</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Ünnerstütt Ünnertitel: Laadt Ünnertitel mit passen Naam automaatsch</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ondersteuning voor ondertitels: automatisch ondertitels laden met de overeenkomstige naam</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Obsługa napisów: Samoczynne wczytywanie napisów o pasującej nazwie</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporte para legendas: Carrega automaticamente as legendas com o nome correspondente</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte a legendas: Carrega as legendas com o nome correspondente de forma automática</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Podpora pre titulky: Automaticky načíta titulky so zhodným názvom</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Титлови: аутоматски учитава титлове са поклапајућим именом.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Titlovi: automatski učitava titlove sa poklapajućim imenom.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Титлови: аутоматски учитава титлове са поклапајућим именом.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Titlovi: automatski učitava titlove sa poklapajućim imenom.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Stöd för textning: Laddar automatiskt textning med motsvarande namn</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">підтримка субтитрів: програма автоматично завантажує субтитри з відповідною назвою;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSupport for subtitles: Automatically loads subtitles with the matching namexx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">支援字幕：名稱相符的話自動載入字幕</li>
      <li>Video display settings (brightness, contrast)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Ajustaments per a la pantalla de vídeo (brillantor, contrast)</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Video display settings (brightness, contrast)</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Opciones de visualización de vídeos (brillo, contraste)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">동영상 표시 설정(밝기, 명암)</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Video-Afspeelinstellen (Helligkeit, Kontrast)</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Instellingen voor het scherm (helderheid, contrast)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Ustawienia wyświetlania obrazu (jasność, kontrast)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Configuração da visualização de vídeo (brilho, contraste)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Configuração da exibição de vídeo (brilho, contraste)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Nastavenia zobrazenia videa (jas, kontrast)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Поставке видео приказа (осветљај, контраст).</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Postavke video prikaza (osvetljaj, kontrast).</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Поставке видео приказа (осветљај, контраст).</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Postavke video prikaza (osvetljaj, kontrast).</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Inställningar av videovisning (ljusstyrka, kontrast)</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">можливість зміни параметрів показу відео (яскравості, контрастності);</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxVideo display settings (brightness, contrast)xx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">影像顯示設定（亮度、對比）</li>
      <li>Due to using Solid and Phonon DragonPlayer is independent of any multimedia framework or hardware abstraction layer</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">A causa de l'ús de Solid i Phonon, el DragonPlayer és independent de qualsevol marc de treball multimèdia o capa d'abstracció de maquinari</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Due to using Solid and Phonon DragonPlayer is independent of any multimedia framework or hardware abstraction layer</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Debido al uso de Solid y Phonon, DragonPlayer es independiente de cualquier framework multimedia o capa de abstracción hardware</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">Dragon 플레이어는 Solid와 Phonon을 사용하므로 멀티미디어 프레임워크와 하드웨어 추상화 계층과 독립적입니다</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Drakenspeler bruukt Solid un Phonon un anners keen Multimedia-Rahmenwark oder Hardware-Afstraktschoonlaag</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Omdat DragonPlayer Solid en Phonon gebruikt is het onafhankelijk van elk multimediaframework of hardware-abstractielaag</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Ze względu na używanie Solid i Phonon Odtwarzacz Dragon jest niezależny od żadnego szkieletu multimedialnego czy warstwy abstrakcji sprzętu</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Devido à utilização do Solid e do Phonon, o DragonPlayer é independente de qualquer plataforma multimédia ou camada de 'hardware'</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Devido ao uso do Solid e Phonon, o Dragon Player independe de qualquer plataforma multimídia ou camada de abstração de hardware</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Kvôli použitiu Solid a Phonon je DragonPlayer nezávislý od akéhokoľvek multimediálneho frameworku alebo vrstvy abstrakcie hardvéru.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Будући да користи Солид и Фонон, Змајев плејер је независан од осталих мултимедијалних радних оквира и слојева апстракције хардвера.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Budući da koristi Solid i Phonon, Zmajev plejer je nezavisan od ostalih multimedijalnih radnih okvira i slojeva apstrakcije hardvera.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Будући да користи Солид и Фонон, Змајев плејер је независан од осталих мултимедијалних радних оквира и слојева апстракције хардвера.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Budući da koristi Solid i Phonon, Zmajev plejer je nezavisan od ostalih multimedijalnih radnih okvira i slojeva apstrakcije hardvera.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">På grund av att Solid och Phonon används är Dragon videospelare oberoende av alla ramverk för multimedia och hårdvaruabstraktionslager</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">оскільки у програмі використовуються бібліотеки Solid та Phonon, її робота не залежить від використаного набору мультимедійних бібліотек та рівня абстрагування від обладнання;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxDue to using Solid and Phonon DragonPlayer is independent of any multimedia framework or hardware abstraction layerxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">因為使用 Solid 與 Phonon，DragonPlayer 可以獨立於任何多媒體框架，或是硬體抽象層之外</li>
      <li>Supports playing CDs and DVDs</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Implementació per a reproduir CD i DVD</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Supports playing CDs and DVDs</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Permite la reproducción de CDs y DVDs</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">CD 및 DVD 재생 지원</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Ünnerstütt dat Afspelen vun CDs un DVDs</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ondersteunt afspelen van cd's en dvd's</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Obsługa odtwarzania płyt CD i DVD</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporte à reprodução de CD's e DVD's</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte a reprodução de CDs e DVDs</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Podpora prehrávania CD a DVD</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Пуштање ЦД‑ова и ДВД‑ова.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Puštanje CD‑ova i DVD‑ova.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Пуштање ЦД‑ова и ДВД‑ова.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Puštanje CD‑ova i DVD‑ova.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Stöder uppspelning av cd- och dvd-skivor</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">підтримка відтворення компакт-дисків та DVD.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSupports playing CDs and DVDsxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">支援播放 CD 與 DVD</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=dragonplayer</url>
  <url type="help">http://docs.kde.org/stable/en/kdemultimedia/dragonplayer/index.html</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>http://kde.org/images/screenshots/dragonplayer.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>dragon</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
