<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>dragonplayer.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Dragon Player</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Dragon Player</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Přehrávač Dragon</name>
  <name xml:lang="nds">Drakenspeler</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Dragon Player</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Odtwarzacz Dragon</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Програвач Dragon</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxDragon Playerxx</name>
  <description>
    <p>
      Dragon Player is a multimedia player where the focus is on simplicity, instead of features. Dragon Player does one thing,
      and only one thing, which is playing multimedia files. It's simple interface is designed not to get in your way and instead
      empower you to simply play multimedia files.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El Dragon Player és un reproductor multimèdia que se centra en la simplicitat, en lloc de les característiques. El Dragon Player fa una cosa, i només una cosa, la qual és reproduir fitxers multimèdia. Té un interfície senzilla, la qual està dissenyada per a que no s'interposi en el vostre camí i que simplement pugueu reproduir els fitxers multimèdia.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nds">Drakenspeler is en Multimedia-Afspeler, bi den de Eenfachheit in'n Vörgrund steiht un nich de velen Funkschonen bito. Drakenspeler deit nau een Saak, un dat is dat Afspelen vun Multimedia-Dateien. De Brukerböversiet schall Di nich in de Mööt kamen, man Di bi't Bruken vun Multimedia-Inholden ünnerstütten.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Dragon Player is een multimediaspeler waar de focus ligt op eenvoud, in plaats van functies. Dragon Player doet een ding en alleen een ding, en dat is afspelen van multimediabestanden. Zijn eenvoudige interface is niet ontworpen om in de weg te zitten en in plaats u de mogelijkheid te geven om gewoon multimediabestanden af te spelen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Odtwarzacz Dragon jest odtwarzaczem multimedialnym, gdzie położono nacisk na prostotę, a nie na możliwości. Odtwarzacz Dragon robi jedną rzecz i tylko jedną tj. odtwarzanie plików multimedialnych. Jego prosty układ sterowania został zaprojektowany tak, aby nie wchodził w drogę, ale aby pomagał przy odtwarzaniu plików multimedialnych.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Програвач Dragon — програма для відтворення мультимедійних даних, основною перевагою якої є простота. Програвач Dragon робить одну річ і лише одну річ, а саме, відтворює файли мультимедійних даних. Простий інтерфейс програми просто не дасть вам зробити щось неправильно, але надасть вам змогу відтворити потрібні вам дані.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxDragon Player is a multimedia player where the focus is on simplicity, instead of features. Dragon Player does one thing, and only one thing, which is playing multimedia files. It's simple interface is designed not to get in your way and instead empower you to simply play multimedia files.xx</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Característiques:</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Vlastnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nds">Markmalen:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Mogelijkheden:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Możliwości:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Можливості:</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxFeatures:xx</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Simple Interface</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Interfície senzilla</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Eenfach Böversiet</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Eenvoudig interface</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Prosty układ sterowania</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">простий інтерфейс;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSimple Interfacexx</li>
      <li>Resuming videos: Starts playing a video where you were watching it last time</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Continua els vídeos: Inicia la reproducció d'un vídeo on l'estàveu veient l'última vegada</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Videos wiederspelen: En Video dor wieder afspelen, woneem Du vördem ophollen hest</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Video's hervatten: begin met het afspelen van een video waar u de laatste keer deze bekeek</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Wznawianie filmów: Rozpoczyna odtwarzane filmu od chwili jego przerwania przy poprzednim oglądaniu</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">поновлення відтворення відео: відео починає відтворюватися з того моменту, на якому ви зупинили відтворення під час попереднього сеансу роботи з програмою;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxResuming videos: Starts playing a video where you were watching it last timexx</li>
      <li>Support for subtitles: Automatically loads subtitles with the matching name</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Implementació per a subtítols: Càrrega automàticament els subtítols que coincideixen amb el nom</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Ünnerstütt Ünnertitel: Laadt Ünnertitel mit passen Naam automaatsch</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ondersteuning voor ondertitels: automatisch ondertitels laden met de overeenkomstige naam</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Obsługa napisów: Samoczynne wczytywanie napisów o pasującej nazwie</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">підтримка субтитрів: програма автоматично завантажує субтитри з відповідною назвою;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSupport for subtitles: Automatically loads subtitles with the matching namexx</li>
      <li>Video display settings (brightness, contrast)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Ajustaments per a la pantalla de vídeo (brillantor, contrast)</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Video-Afspeelinstellen (Helligkeit, Kontrast)</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Instellingen voor het scherm (helderheid, contrast)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Ustawienia wyświetlania obrazu (jasność, kontrast)</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">можливість зміни параметрів показу відео (яскравості, контрастності);</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxVideo display settings (brightness, contrast)xx</li>
      <li>Due to using Solid and Phonon DragonPlayer is independent of any multimedia framework or hardware abstraction layer</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">A causa de l'ús de Solid i Phonon, el DragonPlayer és independent de qualsevol marc de treball multimèdia o capa d'abstracció de maquinari</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Drakenspeler bruukt Solid un Phonon un anners keen Multimedia-Rahmenwark oder Hardware-Afstraktschoonlaag</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Omdat DragonPlayer Solid en Phonon gebruikt is het onafhankelijk van elk multimediaframework of hardware-abstractielaag</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Ze względu na używanie Solid i Phonon Odtwarzacz Dragon jest niezależny od żadnego szkieletu multimedialnego czy warstwy abstrakcji sprzętu</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">оскільки у програмі використовуються бібліотеки Solid та Phonon, її робота не залежить від використаного набору мультимедійних бібліотек та рівня абстрагування від обладнання;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxDue to using Solid and Phonon DragonPlayer is independent of any multimedia framework or hardware abstraction layerxx</li>
      <li>Supports playing CDs and DVDs</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Implementació per a reproduir CD i DVD</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Ünnerstütt dat Afspelen vun CDs un DVDs</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ondersteunt afspelen van cd's en dvd's</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Obsługa odtwarzania płyt CD i DVD</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">підтримка відтворення компакт-дисків та DVD.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSupports playing CDs and DVDsxx</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=dragonplayer</url>
  <url type="help">http://docs.kde.org/stable/en/kdemultimedia/dragonplayer/index.html</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>http://kde.org/images/screenshots/dragonplayer.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>dragon</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
