<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.kde.dragonplayer.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <developer id="org.kde">
    <name translate="no">KDE</name>
  </developer>
  <name>Dragon Player</name>
  <name xml:lang="ar">مشغّل التّنّين</name>
  <name xml:lang="bg">Dragon Player</name>
  <name xml:lang="bs">Dragon plejer</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Dragon Player</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Dragon Player</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Přehrávač Dragon</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">Dragon Player</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Dragon Player</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">Dragon Player</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Dragon Player</name>
  <name xml:lang="eo">Dragon Player</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Dragon Player</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">Dragoni mängija</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">Dragon Player</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Dragon Player</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Dragon Player</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Dragon Player</name>
  <name xml:lang="he">נגן Dragon</name>
  <name xml:lang="hi">ड्रैगन प्लेयर</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">Dragon Player</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">Dragon Player (Reproductor Dragon)</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">Dragon Player</name>
  <name xml:lang="is">Dragon spilari</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Dragon Player</name>
  <name xml:lang="ka">დამკვრელი Dragon</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">Dragon 플레이어</name>
  <name xml:lang="lv">Dragon Player</name>
  <name xml:lang="nb">Dragon Player</name>
  <name xml:lang="nds">Drakenspeler</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Dragon Player</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">Dragon Player</name>
  <name xml:lang="pa">ਡਰੈਗਨ ਪਲੇਅਰ</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Odtwarzacz Dragon</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Dragon Player</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Dragon Player</name>
  <name xml:lang="ro">Dragon Player</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Dragon Player</name>
  <name xml:lang="sa">ड्रैगन प्लेयर</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Prehrávač Dragon</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Dragon Player</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr">Змајев плејер</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-Latn">Zmajev plejer</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Змајев плејер</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Zmajev plejer</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Dragon videospelare</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Dragon</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Програвач Dragon</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxDragon Playerxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">Dragon Player</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">神龍播放器</name>
  <summary>Play video files and streams</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ar">تشغّل ملفات الفيديو والبث المباشر</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Reprodueix fitxers i fluxos de vídeo</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Reproduïx fitxers i fluxos de vídeo</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Reproduzca archivos y transmisiones de vídeo</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Bideo fitxategiak eta korronteak jo</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Toista videotiedostoja ja suoratoistovirtoja</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Lire des fichiers et des flux vidéo</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Reproduza ficheiros e emisións de vídeo</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="he">נגינת קובצי וידאו ושידורי אינטרנט</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">Videofájlok és közvetítések lejátszása</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ia">Reproduce Files e fluxos (streams) video</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Riproduci file e flussi video</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ka">ვიდეოფაილებისა და ნაკადების დაკვრა</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">동영상 파일과 스트림 재생</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lv">Atskaņojiet video datnes un straumes</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Videobestanden en streams afspelen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Predvajaj video datoteke in tokove</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Spela videofiler och strömmar</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Video dosyalarını ve akışlarını oynatın</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Відтворення відеофайлів та потоків відтворення</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxPlay video files and streamsxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">播放视频文件和流媒体</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">播放影片檔案與串流</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Dragon Player is a video player focusing on simplicity instead of features. Its easy-to-use interface is designed to get out of your way and simply play your video files and streams.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">مشغل التنين هو مشغل فيديو يركز على البساطة بدلاً من الميزات. فقد صُممت واجهته سهلة الاستخدام لتبتعد عن طريقك وتشغّل ملفات الفيديو والبث ببساطة.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El Dragon Player és un reproductor de vídeo que se centra en la simplicitat en lloc de les característiques. La seva interfície fàcil d'utilitzar està dissenyada perquè no s'interposi en el vostre camí i que simplement pugueu reproduir els fitxers i fluxos de vídeo.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Dragon Player és un reproductor de vídeo que se centra en la simplicitat en lloc de les característiques. La seua interfície fàcil d'utilitzar està dissenyada perquè no s'interpose en el vostre camí i que senzillament pugueu reproduir els fitxers i fluxos de vídeo.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Dragon Player es un reproductor de vídeo centrado en la simplicidad. Su interfaz fácil de usar se diseñó para apartarse de su camino y simplemente reproducir sus archivos y transmisiones de vídeo.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Dragon Player bideo jotzaile bat da, ezaugarrietan baino sinpletasunean arreta jartzen duena. Bere interfaze erabilerraza zuri trabarik ez egiteko, eta besterik gabe zure fitxategiak eta korronteak jotzeko diseinatuta dago.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Dragon Player on videosoitin, joka keskittyy ominaisuuksien sijaan yksinkertaisuuteen. Sen helppokäyttöinen käyttöliittymä on suunniteltu pysymään poissa tieltä toistaessasi videotiedostoja ja suoratoistovirtoja.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Dragon Player est un lecteur vidéo conçu pour la facilité d'utilisation, plutôt que d'offrir de nombreuses fonctionnalités. Son interface simple est conçue pour ne pas vous embarrasser mais plutôt vous donner la capacité de lire le plus simplement possible des fichiers et des flux vidéo.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Dragon Player é un reprodutor de vídeo que prefire a simplicidade ás funcionalidades. A súa interface ergonómica está deseñada para non molestar e simplemente reproducir ficheiros de vídeo e emisións.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">נגן Dragon הוא נגן וידאו שהמיקוד בו הוא פשטות, במקום עוד יכולות. הממשק הפשוט שלו תוכנן לא להיתקע לך מול הפרצוף ובמקום פשוט לנגן את קובצי הווידאו והתשדירים והתזרימים המקוונים שלך.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A Dragon Player egy olyan videolejátszó, amely a funkciók helyett az egyszerűségre összpontosít. Könnyen használható felületét úgy tervezték, hogy ne legyen útban, és egyszerűen lejátssza a videofájlokat és közvetítéseket.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">Dragon Player es un reproductor multimedial ubi le foco es sur simplicitate, in loco de charactersticas. Su interfacie facile a usar es designate per lassar tu strada e simplemente reproduce tu files e fluxos (/streams) video.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Dragon Player è un lettore video il cui obiettivo è la semplicità, anziché la molteplicità di funzioni. La sua interfaccia semplice è progettata per non metterti in difficoltà e per permetterti semplicemente di riprodurre i file multimediali.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">Dragon Player-ი მულტიმედია დამკვრელია, რომელიც ფუნქციების ნაცვლად აქცენტს სიმარტივეზე აკეთებს. Dragon Player-ის იოლი ინტერფეისი განკუთვნილია, რომ ფეხებში არ გამოგედოთ და უბრალოდ დაუკრას ვიდეოფაილები.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">Dragon 플레이어는 기능보다 간단함에 초점을 맞춘 멀티미디어 재생기입니다. 단순히 동영상 파일과 스트림만을 재생할 수 있도록 사용하기 쉽게 인터페이스를 설계했습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lv">„Dragon Player“ ir video atskaņotājs ar uzsvaru uz vienkāršību, bet ne plašām iespējām. Programmai ir viegli lietojama saskarne, lai ļautu bez liekiem traucēkļiem noskatīties video datnes un straumes.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Dragon Player is een videospeler met de focus op eenvoud in plaats van functies. Zijn gemakkelijk te gebruiken interface is ontworpen om niet in de weg te zitten en gewoon videobestanden en streams af te spelen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Dragon Player je video predvajalnik, ki se osredotoča na preprostost namesto na zmožnosti. Njegov vmesnik, ki je enostaven za uporabo, je zasnovan tako, da se vam umakne in preprosto predvaja vaše video datoteke in tokove.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Dragon videospelare är en videospelare med fokus på enkelhet istället för funktioner. Dess enkla gränssnitt är konstruerat för att inte vara i vägen utan istället ge dig möjlighet att enkelt spela upp videofiler och strömmar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Dragon, özellikler yerine yalınlığa odaklanan bir çoklu ortam oynatıcısıdır. Basit arayüzü, yolunuza çıkmayacak şekilde tasarlanmıştır ve çoklu ortam dosyalarını kolayca oynatmanızı sağlar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Програвач Dragon — відеопрогравач, перевагою якого є простота, а не широкий діапазон можливостей. Його простий у користуванні інтерфейс не заважатиме вам просто переглядати файли відео та потоки даних з мережі.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxDragon Player is a video player focusing on simplicity instead of features. Its easy-to-use interface is designed to get out of your way and simply play your video files and streams.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">Dragon Player 是一款设计简洁的视频播放器，专注于易用性。其界面设计不干扰用户，只专注于视频文件和流媒体的播放。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">神龍播放器是一個注重簡潔而非大量功能的影片播放器。它提供易於使用的介面，讓您能不用在意它而專注在播放您的影片檔案或串流上。</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">الميزات:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ast">Funciones:</p>
    <p xml:lang="bg">Възможности:</p>
    <p xml:lang="bs">Svojstva:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Característiques:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Característiques:</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Vlastnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Funktioner:</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Funktionen:</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Χαρακτηριστικά:</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">Trajtoj:</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Características:</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Omadused:</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Ezaugarriak:</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Ominaisuudet:</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Fonctionnalités :</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">יכולות:</p>
    <p xml:lang="hi">विशेषताएँ:</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">Funkciók:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">Characteristicas:</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Fitur:</p>
    <p xml:lang="is">Eiginleikar:</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Caratteristiche:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">თვისებები:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">기능:</p>
    <p xml:lang="lv">Iespējas:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nb">Funksjoner:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nds">Markmalen:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Mogelijkheden:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">Funksjonar:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pa">ਲੱਛਣ:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Możliwości:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">Caracteristici:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Возможности:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sa">गुणाः:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Funkcie:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Zmožnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Могућности:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-Latn">Mogućnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Могућности:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Mogućnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Funktioner:</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Özellikler:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Можливості:</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxFeatures:xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">功能：</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">功能：</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Click to play or pause, and double-click to enter or exit full screen mode.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">النقر للتشغيل أو الإيقاف المؤقت، وانقر نقرًا مزدوجًا للدخول إلى وضع ملء الشاشة أو الخروج منه.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Feu clic per a reproduir o fer una pausa i feu doble clic per a entrar o sortir del mode de pantalla completa.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Feu clic per a reproduir o fer una pausa i feu doble clic per a entrar o eixir del mode de pantalla completa.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Pulse para reproducir o parar, y haga doble click para entrar o salir del modo pantalla completa.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Egin klik jotzeko edo etenaldirako, eta egin klik bikoitza pantaila-osoko moduan sartzeko edo irteteko.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Toista tai keskeytä napsauttamalla ja siirry koko näytön tilaan tai poistu siitä kaksoisnapsautuksella.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Veuillez effectuer un clic pour lire ou mettre en pause, puis un double clic pour basculer ou sortie du mode « Plein écran ».</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Prema para reproducir ou pausar, e faga clic duplo ou saia do modo a pantalla completa.</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">נא ללחוץ כדי לנגן או להשהות, לחיצה כפולה כדי להגדיל למסך מלא או להקטין חזרה.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Kattintással lejátszás vagy szüneteltetés, dupla kattintással belépés teljes képernyős módba, vagy kilépés onnan.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Clicca per reproducer o pausar, e dupleclicca per entrar o exir de modo a plen texto.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Fai clic per riprodurre o mettere in pausa e fai doppio clic per entrare o uscire dalla modalità a schermo intero.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">დააწკაპუნეთ დასაკრავად, ან შესაჩერებლად. ორმაგი წკაპი სრულ ეკრანზე გადასასვლელად, ან სრული ეკრანის დასატოვებლად.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">클릭하여 재생/일시 정지, 두 번 클릭하여 전체 화면 모드 전환.</li>
      <li xml:lang="lv">Klikšķiniet, lai atskaņotu vai pauzētu, vai veiciet dubultklikšķi, lai ieslēgtu vai izslēgtu pilnekrāna režīmu.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Klik om af te spelen of te pauzeren en dubbelklik om modus volledig scherm in of uit te gaan.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Kliknite za predvajanje ali začasno ustavitev in dvokliknite za vstop ali izhod iz celozaslonskega načina.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Klicka för att spela eller pausa, och dubbelklicka för att gå till eller lämna fullskärmsläge.</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Oynatmak veya duraklatmak için tıklayın ve tam ekran kipine girmek veya çıkmak için çift tıklayın.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Клацання для запуску або призупинення відтворення, подвійне клацання для входу або виходу з повноекранного режиму.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxClick to play or pause, and double-click to enter or exit full screen mode.xx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">点击以播放或暂停，双击进入或退出全屏模式。</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">點擊以播放或暫停，連點兩下來進入或離開全螢幕模式。</li>
      <li>Choose the subtitle language, and automatically load the right one for your language, if possible.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">تختار لغة الترجمة، وتحمل تلقائياً اللغة المناسبة للغتك، إن أمكن.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Trieu l'idioma dels subtítols i carregueu automàticament els adequats de l'idioma que vulgueu, si és possible.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Seleccioneu l'idioma dels subtítols i carregueu automàticament els adequats de l'idioma que vulgueu, si és possible.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Elija el lenguaje de los subtítulos y automáticamente cargará el correcto para su idioma, si está disponible.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Aukeratu azpidatzien hizkuntza, eta zure hizkuntzarako egokia dena automatikoki zamatu, ahal bada.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Valitse tekstityskieli ja yritä automaattisesti ladata oikea.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Veuillez sélectionner la langue de sous-titres et charger automatiquement celle convenant à votre langue, si possible.</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Escolla o idioma dos subtítulos, e cargue automaticamente o do seu idioma de ser posíbel.</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">נא לבחור את שפת הכתוביות ולטעון את המתאימות לשפה שלך אם ישנן.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Felirat nyelvének kiválasztása és lehetőség szerint a nyelvének megfelelő betöltése.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Selige le linguage de subtitulo, e carga automaticamente lo que es correcte per tu linguage, si possibile. </li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Seleziona la lingua dei sottotitoli e, se possibile, carica automaticamente quella giusta per la tua lingua.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">აირჩიეთ სუბტიტრების ენა და ავტომატური ჩატვირთვა თქვენი ენისთვის, თუ ეს შესაძლებელია.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">자막 언어 선택, 사용 가능한 경우 기본 언어로 자막을 표시합니다.</li>
      <li xml:lang="lv">Izvēlieties subtitru valodu un automātiski ielādējiet pareizos subtitrus, ja pieejami.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Kies de taal van de ondertitels en laad automatisch de juiste voor uw taal, indien mogelijk.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Izberite jezik podnapisov in po možnosti samodejno naložite pravega za svoj jezik.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Välj språk för textning, och läs automatiskt in rätt språk, om möjligt.</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Altyazı dilini seçin ve varsa diliniz için olan altyazıyı kendiliğinden yükleyin.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Вибір мови субтитрів та автоматичне завантаження, якщо це можливо, належних субтитрів для вашої мови.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxChoose the subtitle language, and automatically load the right one for your language, if possible.xx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">选择字幕语言，系统会自动加载适合您的字幕 (如果可能)。</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">選擇字幕語言，並在可能的時候自動載入您的語言的字幕。</li>
      <li>Choose the audio track.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">اختيار مقطوعة الصوت.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Trieu la pista d'àudio.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Seleccioneu la pista d'àudio.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Elija la pista de audio.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Aukeratu audio-pista.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Valitse ääniraita.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Veuillez sélectionner la piste audio.</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Escolla a pista de son.</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">בחירת רצועת השמע.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Hangsáv kiválasztása.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Selige le tracia audio.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Scegli la traccia audio.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">აირჩიეთ აუდიობილიკი.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">오디오 트랙을 선택할 수 있습니다.</li>
      <li xml:lang="lv">Izvēlieties skaņas celiņu.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Kies de audiotrack.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Izberite zvočni posnetek.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Välj ljudspåret.</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Ses parçasını seçin.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Вибір звукової доріжки.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxChoose the audio track.xx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">选择音频轨道。</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">選擇音效軌。</li>
      <li>Choose the video track.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">اختيار مسار الفيديو</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Trieu la pista de vídeo.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Seleccioneu la pista de vídeo.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Elija la pista de vídeo.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Aukeratu bideo-pista.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Valitse videoraita.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Veuillez sélectionner la piste vidéo.</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Escolla a pista de vídeo.</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">בחירת רצועת הווידאו.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Videosáv kiválasztása.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Selige le tracia video.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Scegli la traccia video.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">აირჩიეთ ვიდეობილიკი.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">동영상 트랙을 선택할 수 있습니다.</li>
      <li xml:lang="lv">Izvēlieties video celiņu.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Kies de videotrack.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Izberite video posnetek.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Välj videospåret.</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Video parçasını seçin.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Вибір відеодоріжки.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxChoose the video track.xx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">选择视频轨道。</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">選擇影片軌。</li>
      <li>Adjust the volume by scrolling.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">ضبط الصوت بالتمرير.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Ajusteu el volum amb el desplaçament.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Ajusteu el volum amb el desplaçament.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Ajuste el volumen por desplazamiento.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Kiribilduz bolumena doitu.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Säädä äänenvoimakkuutta vierittämällä.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Ajustez le volume par un simple défilement.</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Desprace para axustar o volume.</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">כוונון עוצמת השמע בגלילה.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Hangerő beállítása görgetéssel.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Adapta le volumine per rolar.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Regola il volume scorrendo.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">ხმის გასწორება თაგუნას ბორბლით.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">스크롤하여 음량을 조절할 수 있습니다.</li>
      <li xml:lang="lv">Pārvaldiet skaļumu ar ritināšanu.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Pas het volume aan door te schuiven.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Prilagodite glasnost s pomikanjem.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Justera volymen genom att rulla.</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Sararak ses düzeyini ayarlayın.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Коригування гучності гортанням.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxAdjust the volume by scrolling.xx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">通过滚动调整音量。</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">利用滑鼠捲動來調整音量。</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
  <url type="homepage">https://apps.kde.org/dragonplayer</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=dragonplayer</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/?application=dragonplayer</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=dragon&amp;source=appdata</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/dragonplayer/dragonplayer.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>dragon</binary>
  </provides>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.dragonplayer.desktop</launchable>
  <categories>
    <category>AudioVideo</category>
    <category>Player</category>
  </categories>
  <releases>
    <release version="25.04.3" date="2025-07-03"/>
    <release version="25.04.2" date="2025-06-05"/>
    <release version="25.04.1" date="2025-05-08"/>
    <release version="25.04.0" date="2025-04-17"/>
    <release version="24.12.3" date="2025-03-06"/>
    <release version="24.12.2" date="2025-02-06"/>
    <release version="24.12.1" date="2025-01-09"/>
    <release version="24.12.0" date="2024-12-12"/>
    <release version="24.08.3" date="2024-11-07"/>
    <release version="24.08.2" date="2024-10-10"/>
    <release version="24.08.1" date="2024-09-12"/>
    <release version="24.08.0" date="2024-08-22"/>
    <release version="24.05.2" date="2024-07-04"/>
    <release version="24.05.1" date="2024-06-13"/>
    <release version="24.05.0" date="2024-05-23"/>
    <release version="24.02.2" date="2024-04-11"/>
    <release version="24.02.1" date="2024-03-21"/>
    <release version="24.02.0" date="2024-02-28"/>
    <release version="23.08.5" date="2024-02-15"/>
  </releases>
</component>
